<resources>
    <string name="app_name">London Tour</string>
    <string name="big_ben_name">The Big Ben</string>
    <string name="big_ben_description">Technically, Big Ben is the name given to the massive bell inside the clock tower, which weighs more than 13 tons (13,760 kg).\n + "The clock tower looks spectacular at night when the four clock faces are illuminated.\n"</string>
    <string name="london_eye_name">The London Eye</string>
    <string name="london_eye_description">The London Eye has now become one of the iconic sights of London. Opened in March 2000 the wheel is a metaphor for the turning of the century. \n</string>
    <string name="london_eye_description_2">The London Eye is 135m/443ft high and weighs 2100 tonnes. \n</string>
    <string name="london_eye_description_3">There are 32 capsules attached to the wheel which travels gently at a speed of 26cm per second.</string>
    <string name="buckingham_palace">Buckingham Palace</string>
    <string name="buckingham_description_1">Buckingham Palace is the working headquarters of the Monarchy, where The Queen carries out her official and ceremonial duties as Head of State of the United Kingdom and Head of the Commonwealth.\n</string>
    <string name="buckingham_description_2">The Queen and The Duke of Edinburgh live in the private apartments on the north side of the Palace, while rooms on the upper floors of the north and east sides are occupied by other members of the Royal Family. \n</string>
    <string name="buckingham_description_3">Much of the ground floor and the south wing of the Palace are used by Household staff. The principal State Rooms used for court ceremonies and official entertaining occupy the main west block facing the gardens.</string>
    <string name="jones_name">The Jones Family Project</string>
    <string name="jones_description_1">Situated in the heart of bustling Shoreditch and within strolling distance of Old Street station is The Jones Family Project, an adaptable restaurant and bar venue open from breakfast to midnight and perfect for both work and play.\n</string>
    <string name="jones_description_2">The folks at Jones\' ethos is simple; they\'re out to ensure everyone that steps through the door enjoys sumptuous food and drink in a warm and accommodating atmosphere to get the good times rolling. \n</string>
    <string name="jones_description_3">The interior is slick, clean cut and effortlessly stylish, with a whole host of versatile areas including two Pop Up areas that regularly change theme, offering plenty of excellent options for staging private functions of all shapes and sizes.</string>
    <string name="dead_name">The Dead Doll House</string>
    <string name="dead_description_1">Storming with the success of their Hoxton pop-up, Dead Dolls House adopt a dose of more concrete inspired cavorting as they take the reigns of what once was Islington\'s House of Wolf; transforming it into not only a lovingly hushed replica of their Hoxton kick-off, but a whimsical three floors of fun.\n</string>
    <string name="dead_description_2">Playful and proud, the continued \'Roald Dahl-esque charm\' finds a home in three Islington floors. Boasting signature illustrations and a lush neutral palate with flecks of colour, The Dolls House is split between the ground floor Parlour, 2nd floor Library and Dining Room, and a 3rd floor Ballroom.!</string>
    <string name="blues_name">The Blues Kitchen</string>
    <string name="blues_description_1">Sister to venues in Shoreditch and Brixton, Blues Kitchen Camden is one of our absolute favourites. Located on bustling Camden High Street, this is as much a delicious BBQ restaurant as it is a thriving bar and live music venue.\n</string>
    <string name="blues_description_2">With expertly cooked chicken, burgers, BBQ ribs and catfish jambalaya jostling for air-time on the menu, this is certainly one for the ravenous. You can come for lunch or late-night dining throughout the week, or stop in for some brunch at the weekends.</string>
    <string name="fu_name">Fu Manchu</string>
    <string name="fu_description_1">At weekends in Clapham High Street, about 3am, rowdy drunks spill onto the pavements from score of bars and clubs. Clapham has become a hotspot for bars. A few are for the discerning drinker; many are not.\n</string>
    <string name="fu_description_2">Fu Manchu raises the bar, even though a themed drinking spot is hardly an original idea. Fu Manchu is a fictional Chinese villain; his portrait decorates the entrance to this repurposed railway arch. The theme extends to Chinese screens, dim sum snacks (all you can eat for £19.50 on Sundays), and cocktails with an Asian bent.</string>
    <string name="savoy_name">Savoy Hotel</string>
    <string name="savoy_description_1">The Savoy, a Fairmont-managed five star hotel, is one of the most celebrated of London landmarks, proudly standing on the Northbank of the River Thames. The ballet, opera and theatre of vibrant Covent Garden are just steps away; with the City, world-renowned museums and galleries, and the designer shopping of Knightsbridge and Mayfair within easy reach on foot or by taxi.\n</string>
    <string name="savoy_description_2"><![CDATA[The hotel’s 267 luxury rooms and suites celebrate The Savoy’s dual historical influences, featuring either elegant English Edwardian design or sensational Art Deco style. Many afford breath-taking views across the River Thames, and of iconic London landmarks. Those staying in suites enjoy dedicated Butler service, and all guests have access to spa treatments, a private pool, and 24-hour gym in The Savoy’s Beauty & Fitness. \n]]></string>
    <string name="dorchester_name">The Dorchester Hotel</string>
    <string name="dorchester_description_1">As one of the world’s most iconic luxury hotels, The Dorchester is quite simply the place to be in London. Whether you are staying in one of the exquisite rooms and suites, unwinding in the spa, enjoying Michelin-starred cuisine or indulging in an award-winning afternoon tea, you will experience the epitome of timeless glamour. The Dorchester, which is superbly located in the centre of London and overlooks both Hyde Park and Mayfair, is a favourite choice of celebrities, world leaders, royalty and high society.</string>
    <string name="browns_name">Brown\'s Hotel</string>
    <string name="browns_description">Brown’s Hotel is not only London’s first hotel, but also one of the most illustrious in the city. Since opening on Albemarle Street in 1837, the five-star hotel has hosted esteemed guests, from royals and presidents to world-famous authors. Add your name to the guest book and revel in the history of this classic hotel, which offers first-class facilities, award-winning dining and outstanding service in the heart of the distinguished Mayfair neighbourhood</string>
    <string name="hyde_name">Hyde Park</string>
    <string name="hyde_description_1">Every year millions of Londoners and tourists visit Hyde Park, one of the capital\'s eight Royal Parks.\n</string>
    <string name="hyde_description_2">Hyde Park covers 350 acres and is home to a number of famous landmarks including the Serpentine Lake, Speakers\' Corner and the Diana, Princess of Wales Memorial Fountain.\n</string>
    <string name="hyde_description_3">The park also offers various recreational activities including open water swimming, boating, cycling, tennis and horse riding.</string>
    <string name="regents_name">Regent\'s Park</string>
    <string name="regents_description_1">The Regent\'s Park, designed by John Nash, covers 395 acres and includes Queen Mary\'s Gardens which features more than 12,000 roses of 400 varieties, as well as the gloriously restored William Andrews Nesfield\'s Avenue Gardens.\n</string>
    <string name="regents_description_2">With excellent sports facilities spanning nearly 100 acres it includes the largest outdoor sports area in central London.\n</string>
    <string name="regents_description_3">The park also houses the Open Air Theatre, London Zoo, Primrose Hill, the country\'s largest free to access waterfowl collection and 100 species of wild bird.</string>
    <string name="greenwich_name">Greenwich Park</string>
    <string name="greenwich_description_1">Every year millions of Londoners and tourists visit Greenwich Park, one of the capital\'s eight Royal Parks.\n</string>
    <string name="greenwich_description_2">Greenwich Park hosts the Prime Meridian Line and Royal Observatory as well as being part of the Greenwich Maritime World Heritage Site which is home to The National Maritime Museum and Old Royal Naval College.\n</string>
    <string name="greenwich_description_3">The most historic of all Royal Parks, Greenwich Park dates back to Roman times and was enclosed in 1433. From the statue of General Wolfe the park offers imperious views across the River Thames all the way to St. Pauls Cathedral</string>
</resources>
